Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 4
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 4
- Box: 79, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: 30 ans au service des travailleurs = 30 years in the service of the workers = 30 an~os al servicio de los tabajadores: 1950-1980, Publication (Box 79, Folder 11)
    Language: French; English; Spanish.
- Box: 79, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: 35 years in the service of the interests of the workers, for unity and peace, Publication (Box 79, Folder 12)
    Author: Trade Unions International of Miners and Workers in Energy
  - Item 2: 35 years in the service of the interests of the workers, for unity and peace, Publication (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: 35 years in the service of the interests of the workers, for unity and peace, Publication (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: 35 years in the service of the interests of the workers, for unity and peace, Publication (Box 79, Folder 12)
- Box: 79, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: 30 :1949-1979, Publication (Box 79, Folder 13)
    Author: Trade Unions International of Transport Workers
  - Item 2: 30 :1949-1979, Publication (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: 30 :1949-1979, Publication (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Correspondence: Appeal and the Resolutions adopted at the Commemorative Session and the 31st Session, Publication (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Information Bulletin, 1980; Publication (Box 79, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.4-5
  - Item 6: Information Bulletin, 1981; Publication (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Constitution of the Trade Unions International of Transport Workers (W.F.T.U.), 1977; Publication (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Constitution of the Trade Unions International of Transport Workers (W.F.T.U.), 1977; Publication (Box 79, Folder 13)
- Box: 79, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Public Services, Publication (Box 79, Folder 14)
    Author: Trade Unions International of Public & Allied Employees
    Notes: no. 13
  - Item 2: Public Services, Publication (Box 79, Folder 14)
    Notes: no. 14
  - Item 3: Charter of general principles and demands, of rights, working an demployment conditions and of social guarantees of public employees, 1982; Publication (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Charter of general principles and demands, of rights, working an demployment conditions and of social guarantees of public employees, 1982; Publication (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Statute of the Trade Unions International of Public and Allied Employees: adopted at the 7th International Trades Congress of Public Employees: Prague, October 1982, Publication (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Statute of the Trade Unions International of Public and Allied Employees: adopted at the 7th International Trades Congress of Public Employees: Prague, October 1982, Publication (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Statute of the Trade Unions International of Public and Allied Employees: adopted at the 4th International Trades Congress of Public Employees: Budapest, 8 to 13 April 1968, Publication (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: Social Charter ...: Sofia, March 1988, Publication (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Social Charter...: Sofia, March 1988, Publication (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Charte Sociale, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: Charta Social, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 14)
- Box: 79, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Statute of the Trade Unions International of Public and Allied Employees: adopted at the 7th International Trades Congress of Public Employees: Prague, October 1982, Publication (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Statute6th, 1977; Publication (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Statute6th, 1977; Publication (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Statuts, 1977; Publication (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Statuts, 1977; Publication (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Statuts, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Statuts, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: Stazung, 1977; Publication (Box 79, Folder 15)
    Language: German.
  - Item 9: Stazung, 1977; Publication (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: Estatutos, 1977; Publication (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: Estatutos, 1977; Publication (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Item 12: Statute of the Trade Unions International of Public and Allied Employees: adopted at the 8th International Trades Congress of Public Employees: Sofia March 1988, Publication (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Item 13: Statute of the Trade Unions International of Public and Allied Employees: adopted at the 8th International Trades Congress of Public Employees: Sofia March 1988, Publication (Box 79, Folder 15)
- Box: 79, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Appeal, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    Author: Trade Unions International of Workers in Commerce
  - Item 2: Press Release, 1989; Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: May Day Centenary, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Declaration concerning the ratification of the INF treaty and on the positive results achieved at the Moscow Summit, 1968; Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Solidarity with the workers and their trade union at the transnational tiendas tia in Peru, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Appeal to all commerce trade unions and workers on the occasion of the, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Press Communique, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: Trade Unions International of Workers in Commerce: March 8 - International Women's Day, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Item 9: To all trade union organizations and workers of commerce throughout the world, 1982; Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Item 10: Statuts = Constitution = Estatutos, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
- Box: 79, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Basic document, 1978; Publication (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Basic document, 1978; Publication (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Basic document, 1978; Publication (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Basic document, 1978; Publication (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Document of orientation and action (adopted by the 9th International Conference of Metalworkers Trade Unions, September 24, 1982), Publication (Box 79, Folder 17)
    Author: Trade Unions International of Workers in the Metal Industries
  - Item 6: Document of orientation and action (adopted by the 9th International Conference of Metalworkers Trade Unions, September 24, 1982), Publication (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: Document of orientation and action (adopted by the 9th International Conference of Metalworkers Trade Unions, September 24, 1982), Publication (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: Document of orientation and action (adopted by the 9th International Conference of Metalworkers Trade Unions, September 24, 1982), Publication (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: Automobile workers trade unions, 1982; Publication (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Item 10: 10th World Trade Union Congress: excerpts from speeches and documents, 1982; Publication (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Item 11: TUI Metal's position in the struggle for peace and on the socio-economic aspects of disarmament, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Item 12: TUI Metal's position in the struggle for peace and on the socio-economic aspects of disarmament, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Item 13: Constitution of the Trade Unions International of Workers in the Metal Industry, 1982; Publication (Box 79, Folder 17)
- Box: 79, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Trade Unions International of Workers in the Metal Industry, 1982; Publication (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Trade Unions International of Workers in the Metal Industry, 1982; Publication (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Constitution of the Trade Unions International of Workers in the Metal Industry, 1982; Publication (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Unity Solidarity, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: 10th World Trade Union Congress: excerpts from speeches and documents, 1982; Publication (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Metalworkers unions in action, 1989; Publication (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Metalworkers unions in action, 1989; Publication (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Metalworkers unions in action, 1989; Publication (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: Metalworkers' struggle for disarmament and peace, Publication (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Item 10: Metalworkers' struggle for disarmament and peace, Publication (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Item 11: Metalworkers' struggle for disarmament and peace, Publication (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Item 12: Metalworkers' struggle for disarmament and peace, Publication (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Item 13: 9th International Conference of Metalworkers Trade Unions: Moscow, September 20-24, 1982: Documents, Publication (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Item 14: 9th International Conference of Metalworkers Trade Unions: Moscow, September 20-24, 1982: Documents, Publication (Box 79, Folder 18)
- Box: 79, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Automobile workers trade unions, 1982; Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Automobile workers trade unions, 1982; Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: 9th International Conference of Metalworkers Trade Unions: Moscow, September 20-24, 1982: Documents, Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: 9th International Conference of Metalworkers Trade Unions: Moscow, September 20-24, 1982: Documents, Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: 10th World Trade Union Congress: excerpts from speeches and documents, 1982; Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: Appeal towards the IX th International Conference of the Metalworkers' Trade Unions, 1982; Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: Reports and documents: 11th World Trade Union Congress (Berlin, GDR, 16-22 September 1986), Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Item 8: Economic bulletin, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
- Box: 79, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: IX Conference Internationale des Syndicats des Travailleurs de la Metallurgie, 1982; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
    Notes: broadside
  - Item 2: Press Communique - Employers step up repression against Metalworkers' Unions, 1981; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Correspondence, 1981; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: TUI Metal's Working Group on Disarmament, 1983; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: File - of the Working Group of TUI Metal on Disamament: Political declaration of the Warsaw Treaty Member-States, 1983; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: File - of the Working Group on Disarmament of TUI Metal: to the Parliaments, Governments, Political Parties, and peoples of the World, 1983; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: TUI Metal's position on ending the arms race, on disarmament and their economic and social implication in the Metal Industry, 1980; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: TUI Metal's position on ending the arms race, on disarmament and their economic and social implication in the Metal Industry, 1980; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 9: Press Communique, 1983; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 10: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 11: Correspondence, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 12: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 13: Press Communique, 1983; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 14: Press Communique, 1983; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 15: Press Communique, 1983; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 16: Press Communique, 1983; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 17: Press Communique, 1983; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 18: Press Communique, 1983; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 19: Press Communique, 1983; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 20: Press Communique, 1983; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 21: Press Communique, 1983; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 22: Press Communique, 1983; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 23: Press Communique, 1983; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 24: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 25: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 26: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 27: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 28: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 29: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 30: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 31: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 32: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 33: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 34: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 35: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 36: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.16
  - Item 37: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 38: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 39: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 40: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 41: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 42: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 43: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 44: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 45: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 46: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.18
  - Item 47: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 48: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 49: Press Communique, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 50: Press Communique, 1985; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 51: Press Communique, 1985; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 52: Press Communique, 1985; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 53: Press Communique, 1985; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 54: Press Communique, 1985; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 55: Press Communique, 1985; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 56: Press Communique, 1985; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 57: Press Communique, 1985; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 58: Press Communique, 1985; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 59: Press Communique, 1985; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 60: Press Communique, 1985; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 61: Hands off Nicaragua!, Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 62: Hands off Nicaragua!, Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 63: No to racisme & apartheid, Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
    Notes: post card
  - Item 64: No to racisme & apartheid, Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 65: TUI Metal Bureau Meeting: Resolution on the activities of Metal Industry Trade Unions in the solution of current problems, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 66: TUI Metal Bureau Meeting: Resolution on the struggle by Asian Metalworkers for their vital interests, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 67: TUI Metal Bureau Meeting: Resolution on the struggle by Asian Metalworkers for their vital interests, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 68: Bureau Meeting Resolution on Solidarity with Nicaragua, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 69: TUI Metal Working Group on Disarmament, 1984; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
- Box: 79, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Press Communique, 1989; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Press Communique, 1989; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Press Communique, 1989; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Press Communique, 1989; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: Press Communique, 1989; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: Press Communique, 1989; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: Press Communique, 1989; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 8: Press Communique, 1989; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 9: Press Communique, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 10: Press Communique, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 11: Press Communique, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 12: Press Communique, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 13: Press Communique, 1989; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 14: Press Communique, 1989; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 15: Press Communique, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 16: Press Communique, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 17: Press Communique, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 18: Press Communique, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 19: Press Communique, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 20: Press Communique, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 21: Press Communique, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 22: Press Communique, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 23: Press Communique, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 24: Press Communique, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 25: Press Communique, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 26: Press Communique, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 27: Press Communique, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 28: Press Communique, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 29: Press Communique, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 30: Press Communique, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 31: Press Communique, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 32: Press Communique, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 33: Press Communique, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 34: Press Communique, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 35: Press Communique, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 36: Press Communique, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 37: Press Communique, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 38: Press Communique, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 39: Press Communique, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 40: Press Communique, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 41: Press Communique, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 42: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 43: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 44: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 45: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 46: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 47: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 48: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 49: Press Communique, 1985; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 50: Press Communique, 1985; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 51: Press Communique, 1985; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 52: Press Communique, 1985; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 53: Press Communique, 1985; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 54: Press Communique, 1985; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 55: Press Communique, 1985; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 56: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 57: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 58: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 59: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 60: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 61: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 62: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 63: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 64: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 65: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 66: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 67: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 68: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 69: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 70: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 71: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 72: Press Communique, 1986; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 73: Informations Informaciones, 1989; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
    Author: Union Internationale des Syndicats des Travailleurs de la Metallurgie
  - Item 74: Informations Informaciones, 1989; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 75: Informations Informaciones, 1989; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 76: Informations Informaciones, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 77: Informations Informaciones, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 78: Informations Informaciones, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 79: Informations Informaciones, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 80: Informations Informaciones, 1985; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 81: Press Communique, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 82: Social progress: 50% cut in strategic weapons, Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 83: Documents/Declaration, 1988; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 84: Correspondence, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 85: Correspondence, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 86: Documents: appeal to Metalworkers Trade Unions of the World, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 87: Documents: appeal to Metalworkers Trade Unions of the World, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 88: Documents: appeal to Metalworkers Trade Unions of the World, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 89: Documents: appeal to Metalworkers Trade Unions of the World, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 90: Open letter to Metalworkers' Unions of the World, Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 91: Letter to Metalworkers Unions, Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 92: Open letter to Metalworkers' Unions of the World, Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 93: Communique de Presse, 1987; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)